

MA-336, College Ring 6, Bremen, 28759, Germany

🛘 (+49) 1511-5661770 | 🗷 theparthshukla@gmail.com | 🎢 www.parthshukla.dev | 🖸 theparthshukla | 🛅 theparthshukla

"Do, or do not. There is no try."

# **Summary**

Creative and engaged first year Computer Science student with experience in design and web development. Interested in using my passion for problem solving to build better solutions for challenging tasks and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

## Education

**Jacobs University B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE**  Bremen, Germany

Aug. 2019 - Present

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

SECRETARY OF THE COLLEGE ASSEMBLY

**UWC Mahindra College** 

Pune,India

Mar. 2018 - Jan. 2019

- Facilitated, supported, and coordinated all activities of the student council.
- Developed, promoted, and conducted a variety of extra curricular programs for students.
- Organized and coordinated various fundraising programs and funfair events to generate revenue.
- Planned, arranged, and chaired all meetings with council members, as needed.

### **Leave No Fingerprints**

Mumbai.India

HEAD OF MANAGEMENT AND ORGANISATION

Mar. 2017 - June. 2019

- · Organised multiple comedy events and concerts to raise money for purchasing equipment and dialysis machines for local hospitals.
- Developed and maintained the front end functionality of websites.

### **Ahmedabad Student Parliament**

Ahmedabad,India

**HEAD OF IT AND LOGISTICS** 

Jun. 2017 - May. 2018

- · Arranged and coordinated all on-site logistics, including transportation, accommodations, meals, guest speakers and audiovisual support.
- · Appointed and led a highly skilled IT team to create event infrastructure as well as provide support during the length of the events.

### Honors & Awards

2018	Runner Up, T.C.S IT Wiz	Pune,India
2017	Da Vinci Scholar, World Scholar's Cup	Delhi, India
2017	1st Place, CISCE National Debate Final	Kolkata,India
2017	Student of The Year, Anand Niketan School	Ahmedabad, India

# Skills\_

**Programming** Experienced: JAVA, Python, C++ Basic:C, Haskell, SQL

Tools Experienced:Git

Front-end Experienced: HTML5 Basic: REACT

**Languages** Native: English, Hindi Basic: Spanish, German

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

### **Computers for All**

Pune, India

SERVICE PROGRAM CO-ORDINATOR Aug. 2017 - Jan. 2019

· Set up a functional computer lab and gave basic computer education to people of all age groups in the village of Asade.

PARTH SHUKLA · RÉSUMÉ JULY 22, 2020